<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dr. Dwijendra Nath Bhakat</title>
    <link>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dr. Dwijendra Nath Bhakat</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 15:35:20 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kirtan: Ek Samīkṣātmak Ālōcanā</title>
      <link>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/books/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 15:35:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/books/4/</guid>
      <description>The Kirtan Ghoxa is a collection of poetical works, primarily composed by the medieval saint Srimanta Sankardev meant for community singing in the Ekasarana religion. Its importance in the religion is second only to the primary text, the Bhagavat of Sankardeva.
&amp;lsquo;Kirtan: Ek Samīkṣātmak Ālōcanā&amp;rsquo; is an analysis-based book of Kirtan Ghoxa by Srimanta Sankardev. It is written for college and university students. It is an essay and foundation book of Sankardev’s Kirtan Ghoxa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jagriti</title>
      <link>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/books/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 15:35:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/books/1/</guid>
      <description>‘Jagriti’ includes poems and articles written by thirty writers in Rajbangshi language. This book is the forefront of the Rajbangshi Bhasha Shahityer Aashor (Club of Rajbangshi language and literature) which was established in Gauripur.
First Edition: 1996
Publisher: Rajbangshi Bhasha Shahityer Aashor, Assam</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bhakti Ratnakar Xar</title>
      <link>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/books/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 15:05:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/books/3/</guid>
      <description>Bhakti Ratnakar Xar is a synopsis of the Sanskrit book Bhakti Ratnakar composed by Mohapurux Srimanta Sankardev. In this book, thirty eight excellence of the original book are described briefly. This is a valuable book for all kind of readers.
First Edition : 2003
Publisher: Assam Sahitya Sabha</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sri Sri Sankardev Birasito Bargeet</title>
      <link>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/books/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 15:05:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/books/2/</guid>
      <description>Sri Sri Sankardev Birasito Bargeet gives an introduction of Sarkardev in it’s preface section. It discusses Bargeet’s definition and number, Bargeet’s popularity, Bargeet’s Raag-Taal, Sarkardev’s Bargeet’s subject, Sankardev’s Bargeet’s language, Sondo (rhythm), Alankara (ornament) and it’s significance as high quality music. In addition to the meaning of each of Sankardev’s Bargeet, the syllable of Satriya dance and music, which is prevalent in Bihar is also discussed towards the end of the book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Dwijendra Nath Bhakat</title>
      <link>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/pages/dnbhakat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 10:27:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/pages/dnbhakat/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Dwijendra Nath Bhakat (born 2 February 1954) is a writer, poet and literary critic of Assamese, Rajbangshi and Bengali language. His literary work has been mostly in two fields: 1) Vaishnavite literature and culture and 2) Rajbangshi language, literature and culture.
He worked in Golakganj Chilarai College of Western Assam for more than three decades as Associate Professor of Assamese Language. He has also worked as a Research Guide of MIL (Modern Indian Language) department of Gauhati University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Dwijendra Nath Bhakat</title>
      <link>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/pages/awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 10:27:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/pages/awards/</guid>
      <description>   Year Award Name Organization     2009 Srimanta Sankardev Gobexona Bota Aauni aati Satra, Majuli, Jorhat Assam   2010 Bipin Chakraborty Xonmaan Dhubri, Assam   2012 Brihottor Golakganj Beshoma Rajhua Shombordhona Golakganj, Assam   2013 Minoti Nandi Smriti Puroshkar Coochbihar, West Bengal   2014 Tribritro Puroshkar Coochbihar, West Bengal   2014 Xikkha Bikaash Bota New Delhi   2015 Kriti Xikkhokor Xonmaan Dhubri, Assam   2016 Bishwa Mohabir Chilarai Smarok Bota Nalbari, Assam   2017 Felicitation Koch Rajbangshi Fashion Hunt, Agomani, Assam   2018 Grierson Xonmaan Rajbangshi Bhasha Academy, Information and Culture Department, West Bengal Government   2018 Hemchandra Baruah Xombordhona Assam Sahitya Sabha    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>