<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Dr. Dwijendra Nath Bhakat</title>
    <link>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Dr. Dwijendra Nath Bhakat</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 10:27:39 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Dwijendra Nath Bhakat</title>
      <link>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/pages/dnbhakat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 10:27:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/pages/dnbhakat/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Dwijendra Nath Bhakat (born 2 February 1954) is a writer, poet and literary critic of Assamese, Rajbangshi and Bengali language. His literary work has been mostly in two fields: 1) Vaishnavite literature and culture and 2) Rajbangshi language, literature and culture.
He worked in Golakganj Chilarai College of Western Assam for more than three decades as Associate Professor of Assamese Language. He has also worked as a Research Guide of MIL (Modern Indian Language) department of Gauhati University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Dwijendra Nath Bhakat</title>
      <link>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/pages/awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 10:27:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xcavan.github.io/dnbhakat/en/pages/awards/</guid>
      <description>   Year Award Name Organization     2009 Srimanta Sankardev Gobexona Bota Aauni aati Satra, Majuli, Jorhat Assam   2010 Bipin Chakraborty Xonmaan Dhubri, Assam   2012 Brihottor Golakganj Beshoma Rajhua Shombordhona Golakganj, Assam   2013 Minoti Nandi Smriti Puroshkar Coochbihar, West Bengal   2014 Tribritro Puroshkar Coochbihar, West Bengal   2014 Xikkha Bikaash Bota New Delhi   2015 Kriti Xikkhokor Xonmaan Dhubri, Assam   2016 Bishwa Mohabir Chilarai Smarok Bota Nalbari, Assam   2017 Felicitation Koch Rajbangshi Fashion Hunt, Agomani, Assam   2018 Grierson Xonmaan Rajbangshi Bhasha Academy, Information and Culture Department, West Bengal Government   2018 Hemchandra Baruah Xombordhona Assam Sahitya Sabha    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>